{
    "id": "16b0c20ddc714422924cab4abee66e2c",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ................... a discussion with my boss in the morning.",
            "description": "In the morning usually refers to past time hence, the simple past is preferred with it. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "have had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2a59f6f659d40749a33978f22ae1bab"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ...................... to our proposal.",
            "description": "The present perfect is commonly used to announce news.",
            "answers": [
                "agreed",
                "have agreed",
                "had agreed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75e956a412ea4e24891a2fbc1f83a436"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody knows how he .................... from the prison.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "escape",
                "has escaped",
                "escaped"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "627e70f9ffc24e4e914995b0c3d6acfb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ship has ……………………………….",
            "description": "People drown ships sink.",
            "answers": [
                "sank",
                "sunk",
                "drown",
                "drowned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ccb28eb126340a18cd98a5b1f172c13"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I talked to her I realized that she ....................... depressed",
            "description": "When the main verb is in the past tense, we usually use past tenses in the subordinate clauses as well. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "is",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46cf1a03713640d980f5ebefb9cbb969"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... to him since our last meeting.",
            "description": "The present perfect is used to talk about time up to now. ",
            "answers": [
                "didn't talk",
                "haven't talked",
                "hadn't talked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0dc133d734ca46dc947886728d7c7a71"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................... out every day.",
            "description": "The simple present is used to talk about habits, routines etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "am working",
                "work",
                "have worked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8a83d36407fd4f34abb4517e9611cfe8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither the manager nor his secretary ...................... present in the office.",
            "description": "When we connect two singular subjects with neither/nor, the verb is singular. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3ee2c51d689449ce9de2e6e9ddf88ad8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The quality of life in urban areas ......................... deteriorating.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular noun quality. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bcc928eba17e4574a1db377237d42b40"
        },
        {
            "question": "Even the mightiest .................... prey to death.",
            "description": "The mightiest is a plural expression.",
            "answers": [
                "fell",
                "has fallen",
                "have fallen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "543c8b8ed75a46ae83a643ed6a81b7a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................... here a moment ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c0ee10ffba3e489494760b3cc549cbf0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She .................... yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not return",
                "has not returned",
                "do not return"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2356df714e9041599f31653e57dc9fef"
        }
    ]
}